in this exercise
we are shown an error and asked why the
code we've been given produces this
error
so this is an argument error we're told
that we have the wrong number of
arguments being passed to our execute
method
the method was expecting one argument
and received zero
now this code looks very similar to
previous code
the difference is that we don't have an
ampersand preceding
block because of this ruby is expecting
for
execute to receive a regular argument
not
a block as an argument so this parameter
block
looks like just any other parameter to
ruby
ruby is not expecting it to represent a
block being passed in
and that's why we're receiving an
argument error
when using an ampersand to define this
parameter
ruby knows that it's expecting a block
and now it will run as expected
you